당신은 이와 같은 결과를 얻을 수 있도록 많은
데이터를 학습한 매우 좋은 모델이 필요합니다.
You obviously need a very good
model train on a lot of data
to get this kind of result.
당신이 학습하고 있는 모델은
And it's likely that the model that
you're training in the assignments
이것을 보여줄 만큼 충분한 데이터를
가지고 학습하지 않았습니다.
is just not trained with
enough data to show this.
그러나, 당신은 시도할 수 있습니다.
But you can try.
제가 언급하지 않은 embeddings을
학습하는 다른 방법이 있습니다.
There are many other ways to learn
embeddings that I won't cover.
지금, 우리는 개별 단어에 대한
모델을 가지고 있습니다.
Now, that we have models for
individual words,
우리는 텍스트가 실제로 단어의 연속이라는
사실을 어떻게 다루어야 할까요?
how do we deal with the fact that
text is actually a sequence of words?
지금까지, 모델은 고정된 크기를 입력으로
보고 있습니다.
So far, your models have only looked
at inputs that were a fixed size.
고정된 사이즈란 단어들을 vector로
설정할 수 있다는 의미이고,
Fixed size means you can always
turn things into a vector, and
neural network로 그것을
적용할 수 있습니다.
feed it to your neural network.
당신이 speech나 text와 같이 가변 길이의
sequences을 가지고 있을때
When you have sequences
of varying length,
가변 길이의 데이터를 다룰 수 없습니다.
like speech or text,
you can no longer do that.
이제 무엇을 할까요??
Now what?